<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>

	<htmlContent tag="FERON_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ferons are one of the dominant sentient species on Merra, there known as the Inquisition to many, and are considered the largest authority within the land of Merra. Ferons exist in four natural states: Nymphs (their development state they either turn into workers or warriors), Warriors (the defenders of the hive), Drones (the builders, source of reproduction and the ones that tend to the queen when needed) and The Queen (the source of eggs and the ruling head of the hive). Ferons are the known protectors of Humans in the land of Merra. The reason why is because Feron venom isn't strong enough to transform anything other than humans, so ferons use humans when new members of the hive are needed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="FERON_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
                Nymph: Nymphs are the second stage of development for a naturally made Feron (First being Feron Grub). Typically Nymphs are either tasked with cleaning Feron Warriors or breeding Feron Grubs.
Feron nymphs do not have any visible gender until they're given a role around thirty years of age. When gestating Feron Grubs they typically reside within there breasts until their ready to exit via an opening on the nymph's nipples.
	</p>
	<p>
                Warrior: Warriors are known as dreaded warriors throughout Merra due to there heavy armour and deadly venom. They are made either by being chosen by the queen of the hive or via a Non-Feron person being injected by a warriors venom (which normally kills if enough is injected). Warriors are all female in appearance though have no role in the Feron reproductive cycle.
	</p>
	<p>
                Drones: Drones are known as the "Seed Givers" of every Feron hive, this is because they are the only hive members that have male genitalia. Once a year the queen release pheromones that tell the drone to start breeding with members of the hive. Like the warrior, Drones can transform people by stinging the individual.
	</p>
	<p>
                Queen: There are only three recorded queens in Merra at this moment Elydia, Thalyss and Devora and each are a leader of the faction known as the inquisition. The queen is the main producer of eggs for the hive to maintain it's numbered and dose this yearly. The queen doesn't have a stinger but instead five openings where eggs exit. A person is rarely transformed into a queen, but when such a thing happens it is thought that it is done by the queens "tongue" pumping an aphrodisiac into the female individual.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

</bookText>
